Guide to the Jean-François Bory Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Professional Papers, 1965-2013; Series V; 5; 5 boxes
  - Other Print Material, 2006-2013
    - Suplemen+o: poesia concreta, no.50, 2006 (Box 26 (Oversize), Folder 266)
    - Journal sous officiel, no.51-53, 2012-2013 (Box 25, Folder 258)